http://www.wordprocessingplus.com/policies/index.html

Sue Recommends
TestimonialsSue has been especially helpful in crisis situations–she knows how to get work done! I can dictate a 10-20 page decision which she then types up into a word processing program. She sends it back to me as an e-mail attachment and it’s all ready for me to use, edit or incorporate into other documents. She’s fast, accurate, and understands the terminology.Sherwood Malamud, Arbitrator/MediatorI have been using the services of Word Processing Plus for the better part of nine years.  We use Sue primarily for transcription services.  It is clear that although the work is relatively mundane (and, in many cases repetitive) Sue thinks about what she is doing rather than just transcribing what she thinks she hears. This has not been the case with other experiences of audio-typing both here in-house and elsewhere. It is also encouraging that, when doubt arises, she asks rather than assumes. The quality of work is consistently high. I have also found the speed of the service to be more than satisfactory – one might think that working in different countries with different time zones might present problems–-that has not proved to be the case. I have, on occasions asked Sue to work outside normal hours; this has not presented a problem. Based on my experience, I have no hesitation in recommending the services of Word Processing Plus.Robert Newton, BSc. (Hons.), M.R.I.C.S., Chartered Valuation Surveyor, Bermuda Realty Company LimitedSue has been doing transcription work for us for a while now, and her work is commendable. We’re very happy to have her as a part of our team.Kathy Zengolewicz, Virtual Staff SolutionsNeed Office Equipment? Office Equipment
May
23
Website Terms of Use
By
Suzanne
·
Comments
(0)
WEBSITE TERMS OF USE
1. AGREEMENT
These Terms of Use (“the Agreement”) constitute a legally binding agreement by and between Word Processing Plus (“Word Processing Plus”) and you or your company (in either case, “You” or “Your”) concerning Your use of Word Processing Plus’s website (the “Website”) and the services available through the Website (the “Services”). By using the Website, You represent and warrant that You have read and understood, and agree to be bound by, the Agreement and Word Processing Plus’s {Privacy Policy} (the “Privacy Policy”). IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND THIS AGREEMENT, OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY IT OR THE PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE AND CEASE USING THE SERVICES.
2. PRIVACY POLICY
By using the Website, You consent to the collection of certain information about You, as specified in the {Privacy Policy} and incorporated herein by reference. Word Processing Plus encourages Users of the Website to frequently check Word Processing Plus’s Privacy Policy for changes.
3. CHANGES TO AGREEMENT AND PRIVACY POLICY
Internet and wireless technology and the applicable laws, rules, and regulations change frequently. ACCORDINGLY, WORD PROCESSING PLUS RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE THIS AGREEMENT AND ITS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME UPON NOTICE TO YOU, TO BE GIVEN BY THE POSTING OF A NEW VERSION OR A CHANGE NOTICE ON THE WEBSITE. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO REVIEW THIS AGREEMENT AND THE PRIVACY POLICY PERIODICALLY. IF AT ANY TIME YOU FIND EITHER UNACCEPTABLE, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE AND CEASE USING THE SERVICES. Unless Word Processing Plus obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected by Word Processing Plus after such time as the revised Privacy Policy takes effect, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policies.
4. ELIGIBILITY
BY USING THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD AND ARE OTHERWISE LEGALLY QUALIFIED TO ENTER INTO AND FORM CONTRACTS UNDER APPLICABLE LAW. Any individual using the Website or Services on behalf of a company further represents and warrants that they are authorized to act and enter into contracts on behalf of that company. The Agreement is void where prohibited.
5. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES
The Website may be linked with the websites of third parties (“Third-Party Websites”), some of whom have established relationships with Word Processing Plus and some of whom do not. Word Processing Plus does not have control over the content and performance of Third-Party Websites. WORD PROCESSING PLUS HAS NOT REVIEWED, AND CANNOT REVIEW OR CONTROL, ALL OF THE MATERIAL, INCLUDING COMPUTER SOFTWARE OR OTHER GOODS OR SERVICES, MADE AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES. ACCORDINGLY, WORD PROCESSING PLUS DOES NOT REPRESENT, WARRANT OR ENDORSE ANY THIRD-PARTY WEBSITE, OR THE ACCURACY, CURRENCY, CONTENT, FITNESS, LAWFULNESS OR QUALITY OF THE INFORMATION MATERIAL, GOODS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE THROUGH THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES. WORD PROCESSING PLUS DISCLAIMS, AND YOU AGREE TO ASSUME, ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND LIABILITY FOR ANY DAMAGES OR OTHER HARM, WHETHER TO YOU OR TO THIRD PARTIES, RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES.
YOU AGREE THAT, WHEN LINKING TO OR OTHERWISE ACCESSING OR USING A THIRD-PARTY WEBSITE, YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR: (1) TAKING PRECAUTIONS AS NECESSARY TO PROTECT YOU AND YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEMS FROM VIRUSES, WORMS, TROJAN HORSES, MALICIOUS CODE AND OTHER HARMFUL OR DESTRUCTIVE CONTENT; (2) ANY DOWNLOADING, USE OR PURCHASE OF MATERIAL THAT IS OBSCENE, INDECENT, OFFENSIVE, OR OTHERWISE OBJECTIONABLE OR UNLAWFUL, OR THAT CONTAINS TECHNICAL INACCURACIES, TYPOGRAPHICAL MISTAKES AND OTHER ERRORS; (3) ANY DOWNLOADING, USE OR PURCHASE OF MATERIAL THAT VIOLATES THE PRIVACY OR PUBLICITY RIGHTS, OR INFRINGES THE INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY AND OTHER PROPRIETARY RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES, OR THAT IS SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS, STATED OR UNSTATED; (4) ALL FINANCIAL CHARGES OR OTHER LIABILITIES TO THIRD PARTIES RESULTING FROM TRANSACTIONS OR OTHER ACTIVITIES; AND (V) READING AND UNDERSTANDING ANY TERMS OF USE OR PRIVACY POLICIES THAT APPLY TO THOSE THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES.
6. LICENSE
Except as expressly set forth herein, this Agreement grants You no rights in or to the intellectual property of Word Processing Plus or any other party. The license granted in this section is conditioned on Your compliance with the terms and conditions of this Agreement. In the event that You breach any provision of this Agreement, Your rights under this section will immediately terminate.
7. CONSENT TO RECEIVE EMAIL
By using the Website and the Services, You consent to receive periodic email communications in connection with the Services. If you sign up for any Word Processing Plus email alert or other email publications, you thereby consent to receive periodic email communications from Word Processing Plus regarding virtual assistant resources, special announcements regarding upcoming industry events, new product offers and other matters.
8. USER CONTENT
“User Content” is any content, materials or information, not including Personal Information (as defined in Word Processing Plus’s {Privacy Policy}), that You upload or post to, or transmit, display, perform or distribute by means of, the Website, whether in connection with Your use of Services or otherwise. YOU HEREBY GRANT WORD PROCESSING PLUS AND ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, AFFILIATES, REPRESENTATIVES, SUBLICENSEES, SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS, AND CONTRACTORS (COLLECTIVELY, THE “Word Processing Plus Parties”) A PERPETUAL, FULLY PAID-UP, WORLDWIDE, SUBLICENSABLE, IRREVOCABLE, ASSIGNABLE LICENSE TO COPY, DISTRIBUTE, TRANSMIT, PUBLICLY DISPLAY OR PERFORM, EDIT, TRANSLATE, REFORMAT AND OTHERWISE USE USER CONTENT IN CONNECTION WITH THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITE, SERVICES OR ANY OTHER SIMILAR OR RELATED BUSINESS, IN ANY MEDIUM NOW EXISTING OR LATER DEVISED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION IN ADVERTISING AND PUBLICITY. YOU FURTHER AGREE THAT THE WORD PROCESSING PLUS PARTIES MAY PUBLISH OR OTHERWISE DISCLOSE YOUR NAME AND/OR ANY USER NAME OF YOURS IN CONNECTION WITH THEIR EXERCISE OF THE LICENSE GRANTED UNDER THIS SECTION. YOU AGREE TO WAIVE, AND HEREBY WAIVE, ANY CLAIMS ARISING FROM OR RELATING TO THE EXERCISE BY THE WORD PROCESSING PLUS PARTIES OF THE RIGHTS GRANTED UNDER THIS SECTION, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY CLAIMS RELATING TO YOUR RIGHTS OF PERSONAL PRIVACY AND PUBLICITY. YOU WILL NOT BE COMPENSATED FOR ANY EXERCISE OF THE LICENSE GRANTED UNDER THIS SECTION. You hereby represent and warrant that You own all rights, title and interest in and to User Content or are otherwise authorized to grant the rights provided the Word Processing Plus Parties under this section.
9. OBJECTIONABLE CONTENT
You represent and warrant that you shall not use the Website or Services to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute any content, information or materials that: (a) are libelous, defamatory, abusive, or threatening, excessively violent, harassing, obscene, lewd, lascivious, filthy, pornographic, may constitute child pornography, may solicit personal information from or exploit in a sexual or violent manner anyone under the age of 18, or are otherwise objectionable; (b) advocate or encourage conduct that could constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any applicable local, state, national, or foreign law or regulation; (c) advertise or otherwise solicit funds or constitute a solicitation for goods or services; or (d) violate any provision of this Agreement or any other Word Processing Plus agreement or policy (collectively, “Objectionable Content”). Word Processing Plus may monitor the Website for Objectionable Content. Without limiting any of its other remedies, Word Processing Plus reserves the right to terminate Your use of the Website and Services or Your uploading, posting, transmission, display, performance or distribution of Objectionable Content. Word Processing Plus, in its sole discretion, may delete any Objectionable Content from its servers. Word Processing Plus intends to cooperate fully with any law enforcement officials or agencies in the investigation of any violation of this Agreement or of any applicable laws.
10. PROHIBITED USES
Word Processing Plus imposes certain restrictions on Your use of the Website and the Services. You represent and warrant that you will not: (a) violate or attempt to violate any security features of the Website or Services; (b) access content or data not intended for You, or log onto a server or account that You are not authorized to access; (c) attempt to probe, scan, or test the vulnerability of the Services, the Website, or any associated system or network, or breach security or authentication measures without proper authorization; (d) interfere or attempt to interfere with the use of the Website or Services by any other user, host or network, including, without limitation by means of submitting a virus, overloading, “flooding,” “spamming,” “mail bombing,” or “crashing”; (e) use the Website or Services to send unsolicited e-mail, including without limitation promotions or advertisements for products or services; (f) forge any TCP/IP packet header or any part of the header information in any e-mail or in any uploading or posting to, or transmission, display, performance or distribution by means of, the Website or Services; or (g) attempt to modify, reverse-engineer, decompile, disassemble or otherwise reduce or attempt to reduce to a human-perceivable form any of the source code used by the Word Processing Plus Parties in providing the Website or Services. Any violation of this section may subject You to civil and/or criminal liability.
11. REFUND POLICY
Purchases of Services will not be refunded except as specifically set forth on the Website or in any other agreement between You and Word Processing Plus. All purchases or service fees are final.
12. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY
(a) Compliance with Law
You represent and warrant that, when using the Website and Services, You will obey the law and respect the intellectual property rights of others. Your use of the Website and Services is at all times governed by and subject to laws regarding copyright ownership and use of intellectual property generally. You agree not to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute any content, information or other materials in violation of any third party’s copyrights, trademarks, or other intellectual property or proprietary rights. YOU SHALL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY VIOLATIONS OF ANY LAWS AND FOR ANY INFRINGEMENTS OF THIRD-PARTY RIGHTS CAUSED BY YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES. THE BURDEN OF PROVING THAT CONTENT, INFORMATION OR OTHER MATERIALS DO NOT VIOLATE ANY LAWS OR THIRD-PARTY RIGHTS RESTS SOLELY WITH YOU.
(b) Copyrighted Materials; Copyright Notice
All Content and other materials available through the Website and Services, including without limitation the Word Processing Plus logo, design, text, graphics, and other files, and the selection, arrangement and organization thereof, are either owned by Word Processing Plus or are the property of Third-Party Service Providers or Word Processing Plus’s other licensors and suppliers. Except as explicitly provided, neither Your use of the Website and Services nor this Agreement grant You any right, title or interest in or to any such materials. Copyright © 2011 to the present, Suzanne Faris, Word Processing Plus LLC. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
(c) Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) Policy
As Word Processing Plus asks others to respect Word Processing Plus’s intellectual property rights, Word Processing Plus respects the intellectual property rights of others. If you have evidence, know, or have a good faith belief that your rights or the rights of a third party have been violated and you want Word Processing Plus to delete, edit, or disable the material in question, you must provide Word Processing Plus with all of the following information: (a) a physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the exclusive right that is allegedly infringed; (b) identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works; (c) identification of the material that is claimed to be infringed or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit Word Processing Plus to locate the material; (d) information reasonably sufficient to permit Word Processing Plus to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and if available, an electronic mail address at which you may be contacted; (e) a statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and (f) a statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. For this notification to be effective, you must provide it to Word Processing Plus’s designated agent at:
DMCA AGENT
Suzanne Faris, Word Processing Plus LLC.
4153 Lookout Trail
Mc Farland, WI 53558
sue@wordprocessingplus.com
13. DISCLAIMERS; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
(a) NO WARRANTIES
WORD PROCESSING PLUS, ON BEHALF OF ITSELF AND ITS LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS, HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES. THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE.” TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. WORD PROCESSING PLUS, ON BEHALF OF ITSELF AND ITS LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS, EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, REGARDING THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT. NEITHER WORD PROCESSING PLUS NOR ITS LICENSORS OR SUPPLIERS WARRANTS THAT THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR THAT THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. NEITHER WORD PROCESSING PLUS NOR ITS LICENSORS OR SUPPLIERS HAS ANY LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES.
(b) YOUR RESPONSIBILITY FOR DAMAGE
YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. YOU WILL NOT HOLD WORD PROCESSING PLUS OR ITS LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS, AS APPLICABLE, RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE THAT RESULTS FROM YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY DAMAGE TO ANY OF YOUR COMPUTERS OR DATA. THE INFORMATION AND SERVICES MAY CONTAIN BUGS, ERRORS, PROBLEMS OR OTHER LIMITATIONS.
(c) LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
THE LIABILITY OF WORD PROCESSING PLUS LLC AND ITS LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS IS LIMITED. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL WORD PROCESSING PLUS OR ITS LICENSORS OR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA OR CONFIDENTIAL OR OTHER INFORMATION, LOSS OF PRIVACY, FAILURE TO MEET ANY DUTY INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION OF GOOD FAITH OR OF REASONABLE CARE, NEGLIGENCE, OR OTHERWISE, REGARDLESS OF THE FORESEEABILITY OF THOSE DAMAGES OR OF ANY ADVICE OR NOTICE GIVEN TO WORD PROCESSING PLUS OR ITS THIRD-PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS, LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS) ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES. THIS LIMITATION SHALL APPLY REGARDLESS OF WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARISE OUT OF BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY OR FORM OF ACTION. ADDITIONALLY, THE MAXIMUM LIABILITY OF WORD PROCESSING PLUS AND ITS LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS TO YOU UNDER ALL CIRCUMSTANCES WILL BE EQUAL TO THE AGGREGATE PRICE YOU PAID TO WORD PROCESSING PLUS DURING THE YEAR PRECEDING THE INCIDENT OR INCIDENTS GIVING RISE TO SUCH LIABILITY. YOU AGREE THAT THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY REPRESENTS A REASONABLE ALLOCATION OF RISK AND US A FUNDAMENTAL ELEMENT OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN WORD PROCESSING PLUS LLC AND YOU. THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES WOULD NOT BE PROVIDED WITHOUT SUCH LIMITATIONS.
(d) APPLICATION
THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, WAIVERS AND LIMITATIONS DO NOT IN ANY WAY LIMIT ANY OTHER DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES OR ANY OTHER LIMITATION OF LIABILITY IN ANY OTHER AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND WORD PROCESSING PLUS OR BETWEEN YOU AND ANY OF WORD PROCESSING PLUS’S LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS. SOME JURISDICTIONS MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, WAIVERS AND LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. UNLESS LIMITED OR MODIFIED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE FOREGOING DISCLAIMERS, WAIVERS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED, EVEN IF ANY REMEDY FAILS ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE. WORD PROCESSING PLUS’S THIRD-PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS, LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS ARE INTENDED THIRD-PARTY BENEFICIARIES OF THESE DISCLAIMERS, WAIVERS AND LIMITATIONS. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR OTHERWISE SHALL ALTER ANY OF THE DISCLAIMERS OR LIMITATIONS STATED IN THIS SECTION.
14. GENERAL REPRESENTATION AND WARRANTY
You represent and warrant that Your use of the Website and Services will be in accordance with this Agreement and any other Word Processing Plus policies, and with any applicable laws or regulations.
15. INDEMNITY BY YOU
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Word Processing Plus and its officers, directors, employees, agents, affiliates, representatives, sublicensees, successors, assigns, contractors and Third-Party Service Providers (collectively, the “Word Processing Plus Parties”) from and against any and all claims, actions, demands, causes of action and other proceedings (collectively, “Claims”), including but not limited to legal costs and fees, arising out of or relating to: (1) Your breach of this Agreement, including without limitation any representation or warranty contained in this Agreement; (2) Your access to or use of the Website or Services; or (3) Your provision to Word Processing Plus or any of the Word Processing Plus Parties of information or other data. The Word Processing Plus Parties will have the right, but not the obligation, to participate through counsel of their choice in any defense by You of any Claim as to which You are required to defend, indemnify or hold harmless the Word Processing Plus Parties. You may not settle any Claim without the prior written consent of the concerned Word Processing Plus Parties.
16. GOVERNING LAW; JURISDICTION AND VENUE
The Website, Services, and this Agreement, including without limitation this Agreement’s interpretation, shall be treated as though this Agreement were executed and performed in Aurora, Colorado USA and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the United States of America without regard to its conflict of law principles. ANY CAUSE OF ACTION BY YOU ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE WEBSITE, SERVICES, ALL ADVERTISING RELATING THERETO, OR THIS AGREEMENT MUST BE INSTITUTED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION AROSE OR BE FOREVER WAIVED AND BARRED. ALL ACTIONS SHALL BE SUBJECT TO THE LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN ABOVE. The language in this Agreement shall be interpreted in accordance with its fair meaning and not strictly for or against either party. THE PROPER VENUE FOR ANY JUDICIAL ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE WEBSITE, SERVICES, ALL ADVERTISING RELATING THERETO, OR THIS AGREEMENT WILL BE THE STATE AND FEDERAL COURTS LOCATED IN OR NEAREST TO MADISON, WISCONSIN USA. THE PARTIES HEREBY STIPULATE TO, AND AGREE TO WAIVE ANY OBJECTION TO, THE PERSONAL JURISDICTION AND VENUE OF SUCH COURTS, AND FURTHER EXPRESSLY SUBMIT TO EXTRATERRITORIAL SERVICE OF PROCESS.
17. TERMINATION
Either party may terminate this Agreement and its rights hereunder at any time, for any or no reason at all, by providing to the other party notice of its intention to do so, in the manner required by this Agreement. This Agreement shall automatically terminate in the event that You breach any of this Agreement’s representations, warranties or covenants. Such termination shall be automatic, and shall not require any action by Word Processing Plus. Upon termination, all rights and obligations created by this Agreement will terminate. For clarification, termination of this Agreement will not relieve You of Your obligation to pay any fees owed Word Processing Plus or any Third-Party Service Provider.
18. NOTICES
All notices required or permitted to be given under this Agreement must be in writing. Word Processing Plus shall give any notice by email sent to the most recent email address, if any, provided by the intended recipient to Word Processing Plus. YOU BEAR THE SOLE RESPONSIBILITY OF ENSURING THAT YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS ON FILE WITH WORD PROCESSING PLUS IS ACCURATE AND CURRENT, AND NOTICE TO YOU SHALL BE DEEMED EFFECTIVE UPON THE SENDING BY WORD PROCESSING PLUS OF AN EMAIL TO THAT ADDRESS. You shall give any notice to Word Processing Plus by means of: (1) hand delivery; (2) certified U.S. mail, return receipt requested, postage prepaid; or (3) overnight courier, each as sent to [4153 Lookout Trail, Mc Farland, WI 53558]. You agree that any notice received from Word Processing Plus electronically satisfies any legal requirement that such notice be in writing.
19. GENERAL
This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between Word Processing Plus and You concerning Your use of the Websites. This Agreement and any other written agreements executed between You and Word Processing Plus or any Third-Party Service Providers constitute the entire agreement concerning Your use of the Services. This Agreement may only be modified by a written amendment signed by an authorized executive of Word Processing Plus or by the unilateral amendment of this Agreement by Word Processing Plus and by the posting by Word Processing Plus of such amended version. If any part of this Agreement is held invalid or unenforceable, that part will be construed to reflect the parties’ original intent, and the remaining portions will remain in full force and effect. A waiver by either party of any term or condition of this Agreement or any breach thereof, in any one instance, will not waive such term or condition or any subsequent breach thereof. This Agreement and all of Your rights and obligations hereunder will not be assignable or transferable by You without the prior written consent of Word Processing Plus. This Agreement will be binding upon and will inure to the benefit of the parties, their successors and permitted assigns. You and Word Processing Plus are independent contractors, and no agency, partnership, joint venture or employee-employer relationship is intended or created by this Agreement. Except for the Word Processing Plus Parties as and to the extent set forth in Sections 14, 19 and 22(e), and Word Processing Plus’s Third-Party Service Providers, licensors and suppliers as and to the extent expressly set forth in Section 17, there are no third-party beneficiaries to this Agreement. You acknowledge and agree that any actual or threatened breach of this Agreement or infringement of proprietary or other third party rights by You would cause irreparable injury to Word Processing Plus and Word Processing Plus’s Third-Party Service Providers, licensors and suppliers, and would therefore entitle Word Processing Plus or Word Processing Plus’s Third-Party Service Providers, licensors or suppliers, as the case may be, to injunctive relief.
PRIVACY POLICY
Word Processing Plus is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the Website (all capitalized terms not defined in this Notice have the same meanings as in Word Processing Plus’s Website Terms of Use. Word Processing Plus created this Privacy Policy to give You confidence as You visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.
This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website and not to any Third-Party Websites, which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.
BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.
Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below.
1. ELIGIBILITY TO USE WEBSITE AND SERVICES
As stated in the Website Terms of Use, use of the Website and Services is restricted to individuals 18 years old and older. Word Processing Plus does not intend to, and will not knowingly, collect information from or about individuals under the age of 18.
2. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES
(a) Traffic Data. Like most website operators, Word Processing Plus automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Website; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You.
(b) Cookies. A “Cookie” is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website. Word Processing Plus uses Cookies to customize Your experience on the Website to Your interests, to ensure that You do not see the same advertisements or informational messages repeatedly, and to store Your password so You do not have to re-enter it each time You visit the Website. For additional information on Word Processing Plus’s uses of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies, below.
IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.
(c) Personal Information. In order for You to use certain of the Services, You may be asked to provide Word Processing Plus with certain information that personally identifies You (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) “Contact Data” (such as Your name, mailing address, phone number, and e-mail address); (2) “Financial Data” (such as Your credit card number or Pay-Pal account number); and (3) “Demographic Data” (such as Your zip code, age, and income). In each case, You will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Website will not gather it surreptitiously. Word Processing Plus may supplement the Personal Information You provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to Word Processing Plus.
You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent You from using certain of the Services.
(d) Information You Make Public. The Website may contain features, including without limitation, public profiles, chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups that permit You to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other, including Your Personal Information. Any information that You choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which Word Processing Plus is unable to exercise control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose Your Personal Information by means of such features, and You agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.
3. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES
(a) Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies
Word Processing Plus analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help Word Processing Plus better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Word Processing Plus is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements. From time to time, Word Processing Plus may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. Word Processing Plus does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information.
(b) Personal Information
(i) Generally. Word Processing Plus uses Your Contact Data to send You information about Word Processing Plus and Word Processing Plus’s products and services, and to contact You when necessary in connection with the Services. Word Processing Plus uses Your Financial Data to verify Your qualifications for certain Services and to bill You. Word Processing Plus uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Website. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time Word Processing Plus may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.
(ii) Disclosure in Connection with Services. Word Processing Plus discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide Services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security.
(iii) License to User Content. As stated in the Website Terms of Use, by using the Website, You grant the Word Processing Plus Parties the right to publish Your name and any username of Yours in connection with the Word Processing Plus Parties’ exercise of their license in and to Your User Content. You further waive any claims arising from the Word Processing Plus Parties’ exercise of that right. For additional information, see Terms of Use Section 8, regarding User Content.
(iv) Other Disclosure. Except under the following circumstances, Word Processing Plus will keep Your Personal Information private, and will not disclose it to third parties:
· By Law or to Protect Rights. Word Processing Plus discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Word Processing Plus believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Word Processing Plus, third parties or the public at large.
* Business Transfers; Bankruptcy. Word Processing Plus reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Word Processing Plus’s assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Word Processing Plus’s successor organization.
* Unpaid Accounts. If You fail to pay any balance owed in consideration of Services, Word Processing Plus may, as permitted by law, report Your Personal Information, including without limitation Your unpaid balance, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies and others.
4. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Word Processing Plus has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information.
5. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
Word Processing Plus wants Your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. As stated in the Website Terms of Use, by using the Website, You represent and warrant that all information You provide on any registration form or otherwise in connection with Your use of the Website and Services will be complete and accurate, and that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy.
6. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES
Word Processing Plus neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by Word Processing Plus. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy.
7. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Word Processing Plus reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. Unless Word Processing Plus obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy.
Effective Date: [April 1, 2011]
Categories :
Comments (0)
Connect with me
Recycle Your Content!http://www.wordprocessingplus.comSave Time &
Money! Learn
How to Recycle
Your Content.Kindle Book Publishinghttp://www.wordprocessingplus.comFind profitable
Kindle niches, get
free traffic & tons
of qualified reviews. Make Your Content Look Awesome!http://www.wordprocessingplus.comGet a monthly newsletter full of idea, quotes, stock photos and backgrounds to help get your message looked at. List Building with Giveaway Eventshttp://www.wordprocessingplus.comLearn how to Add Thousands of New Leads to Your Business, Fast!
Deal of the Day!
Some of the links in the post above are “affiliate links.” This means if you click on the link and purchase the item, we will receive an affiliate commission. Regardless, we only recommend products or services we believe will add value to our readers.
Word Processing Plus LLC
Copyright © 2015 All Rights Reserved
Flexx Theme by iThemesPowered by WordPress
